http://www.ezsniper.com/privacy.php3

Loading...
Privacy/Security Policy
Our policy is to gather and retain as little information about you as possible.
EZ sniper requires three pieces of information from you to open an account: a username you create, a
password you create, and your email address. Your eBay® user name is all that is required for you to
snipe with us on eBay. We don't need your eBay password. Your e-mail address is used only to contact
you with issues relating to the use and operation of EZ sniper.
Bidding results are tabulated for use in the promotion of EZ sniper services. Specific user's information is
not associated with this data. No data is collected on the items you bid on. No demographic information is
collected by EZ sniper. No personal information like name, address, etc. is collected by EZ sniper, and
the information collected by EZ sniper is never made available to third parties.
EZ sniper puts a cookie on your computer which identifies you as a registered users. It is only used to
give you access to our services and is not made available or accessible to third parties.
Payment to EZ sniper is done through our paymaster, Paypal and Stratus. Payer's personal information is
not retained by EZ sniper. Payment information is transmitted to and from Paypal and Stratus utilizing
Secure Socket Layer encryption software.
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from EZ sniper (the “Site”).
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address, and phone number.
We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).
Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
Communicate with you;
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.
We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:
https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.
You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.
For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by:
FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:
http://optout.aboutads.info/.
A list of potential third parties is here
DO NOT TRACK
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
YOUR RIGHTS
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.
Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
DATA RETENTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
MINORS
The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 13.
CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT US
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by using this form.
AD NETWORK INFO
Google - https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/
Aarki - http://corp.aarki.com/privacy
Adacado - https://www.adacado.com/privacy-policy-april-25-2018/
Adara Media - https://adara.com/2018/04/10/adara-gdpr-faq/
AdClear - https://www.adclear.de/datenschutzerklaerung/
ADEX - http://theadex.com
Adform - https://site.adform.com/uncategorized/product-and-services-privacy-policy/
Adobe Advertising Cloud - https://www.adobe.com/privacy/general-data-protection-regulation.html
AdRoll, Inc. - https://www.adroll.com/gdpr
AdTriba - https://privacy.adtriba.com/
advanced STORE GmbH - https://www.ad4mat.com/en/privacy/
Adventori - https://www.adventori.com/fr/avec-nous/mentions-legales/
advolution.control - http://advolution.de/privacy.php
affilinet - https://www.affili.net/uk/footeritem/privacy-policy
Akamai - http://www.akamai.com/compliance/privacy
Amazon - https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010
Amobee - https://www.amobee.com/trust/privacy-guidelines
Analights - https://analights.com/docs/analights-consent-to-the-processing-of-personal-data-en.pdf
AppLovin Corp. - https://www.applovin.com/privacy
AppNexus - https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy
Arrivalist - https://www.arrivalist.com/privacy#gdpr
AudienceProject - http://privacy.audienceproject.com/for-users/
Aunica - http://www.aunica.com/privacy/privacy.html
Avocet - http://avocet.io/privacy-portal
Batch Media - http://batch.ba/datenschutzerklarung/
BDSK Handels GmbH & Co. KG - https://www.xxxlutz.de/ocms/privacy
Beeswax - https://www.beeswax.com/privacy.html
Betgenius - http://betting.geniussports.com/connextra-service-terms-conditions/
Bidswitch - http://www.bidswitch.com/privacy-policy/
Blismedia - http://www.blis.com/privacy/
Bombora - http://bombora.com/privacy
Booking.com - https://www.booking.com/content/privacy.en-gb.html
Cloud Technologies - http://green.erne.co/assets/PolicyCT.pdf
Cloudflare - https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/
Commanders Act - https://www.commandersact.com/en/privacy/
comScore - https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy
Conversant/CJ Affiliate - https://www.conversantmedia.eu/legal/privacy-policy
Crimtan - https://crimtan.com/privacy-ctl/
Criteo - https://www.criteo.com/privacy/
CUBED - http://cubed.ai/privacy-policy/gdpr/
DataXu - https://www.dataxu.com/gdpr/
Delta Projects - http://www.deltaprojects.com/data-collection-policy/
Demandbase - https://www.demandbase.com/privacy-policy/
DENTSU - http://www.dentsu.co.jp/terms/data_policy.html
Dentsu Aegis Network - http://www.dentsu.com/termsofuse/data_policy.html
Digiseg - http://www.digiseg.io/GDPR/
DMA Institute - https://www.dma-institute.com/privacy-compliancy/
DoubleVerify - https://www.doubleverify.com/privacy/
Dstillery - https://dstillery.com/privacy-policy/
DTS - https://client.adhslx.com/privacy.html
EASYmedia - https://www.rvty.net/gdpr
eBay - https://www.ebay.com/help/policies/member-behaviour-policies/user-privacy-notice-privacy-policy?id=4260#section12
ebuilders - http://ebuilders.nl/privacy
Effinity - https://www.effiliation.com/politique-confidentialite.html
emetriq - https://www.emetriq.com/datenschutz/
Ensighten - https://www.ensighten.com/privacy-policy/
Essens - https://essens.no/privacy-policy/
ESV - https://www.wizaly.com/terms-of-use#privacy-policy
Evidon - https://www.evidon.com/resources/privacy-statement/
Exactag - https://www.exactag.com/en/data-privacy/
Exponential - http://exponential.com/privacy/
Facebook - https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update
Flashtalking - http://www.flashtalking.com/first-party-ad-serving/
Fractional Media - https://www.fractionalmedia.com/privacy-policy
FUSIO BY S4M - http://www.s4m.io/privacy-policy/
Gemius - https://www.gemius.com/cookie-policy.html
GfK - https://sensic.net/
GP One - http://www.gsi-one.org/templates/gsi/en/files/privacy_policy.pdf
GroupM - https://www.groupm.com/privacy-policy
gskinner - https://createjs.com/legal/privacy.html
Haensel AMS - https://haensel-ams.com/data-privacy/
Havas Media France - DBi - http://www.centraltag.com/commercial/policy/index.action
hurra.com - http://www.hurra.com/impressum
IBM - https://www.ibm.com/customer-engagement/digital-marketing/gdpr
Ignition One - https://www.ignitionone.com/privacy-policy/gdpr-subject-access-requests/
Impact - https://impact.com/privacy-policy/
Index Exchange - http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/
Infectious Media - https://impressiondesk.com/
Innovid - http://www.innovid.com/privacy-policy
Integral Ad Science - http://www.integralads.com/privacy-policy
intelliAd - https://www.intelliad.de/datenschutz
Interpublic Group - https://www.interpublic.com/privacy-notice
Jivox - http://www.jivox.com/privacy/
Kantar - https://www.kantarmedia.com/global/privacy-statement
Macromill group - https://www.metrixlab.com/privacy-statement/
MainADV - http://www.mainad.com/privacy-policy
Manage.com - https://www.manage.com/privacy-policy/
Marketing Science Consulting Group, Inc. - http://mktsci.com/privacy_policy.htm
MBR Targeting Gmbh - https://privacy.mbr-targeting.com
MediaMath - http://www.mediamath.com/privacy-policy/
Meetrics - https://www.meetrics.com/en/data-privacy/
MindTake Research - https://www.mindtake.com/en/reppublika-privacy-policy
Neodata Group - https://www.neodatagroup.com/en/security-policy
Nielsen - http://www.nielsen.com/us/en/privacy-statement/digital-measurement.html
Nordic Factory Solutions AB - https://www.bannerflow.com/privacy
numberly - http://ads.1000mercis.com/us.html
Oath - https://policies.oath.com/xw/en/oath/privacy/enterprise/b2bprivacypolicy/
Objective Partners - https://www.objectivepartners.com/cookie-policy-and-privacy-statement/
Omnicom Media Group - https://www.omnicommediagroup.com/disclaimer.htm
On Device Research - https://ondeviceresearch.com/GDPR
OneTag - https://www.onetag.net/privacy/
OpenX Technologies - https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/
Optomaton - http://optomaton.com/privacy.html
Oracle Data Cloud - https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/marketing-cloud-data-cloud-privacy-policy.html
OTTO - https://www.otto.de/shoppages/service/datenschutz
PERMODO - http://permodo.com/de/privacy.html
Pixalate - http://www.pixalate.com/privacypolicy/
Platform161 - https://platform161.com/cookie-and-privacy-policy/
PMG - https://www.pmg.com/privacy-policy/
Protected Media - http://www.protected.media/privacy-policy/
Rakuten Marketing - https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy
Rubicon Project - http://rubiconproject.com/rubicon-project-yield-optimization-privacy-policy/
Salesforce DMP - https://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/
Scenestealer - http://www.scenestealer.tv/privacy-policy
Scoota - http://scoota.com/privacy-policy/
Seenthis - https://seenthis.co/privacy-notice-2018-04-18.pdf
Sojern - https://www.sojern.com/privacy/product-privacy-policy/
Sovrn - https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/
Spotad - http://www.spotad.co/privacy-policy/
SpotX - https://www.spotx.tv/privacy-policy/
TabMo - http://static.tabmo.io.s3.amazonaws.com/privacy-policy/index.html
Taboola - https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy
TACTIC™ Real-Time Marketing - http://tacticrealtime.com/privacy/
Teads.TV - https://teads.tv/privacy-policy/
TEEMO - https://teemo.co/fr/confidentialite/
The Trade Desk - https://www.thetradedesk.com/general/privacy-policy
Tradedoubler - http://www.tradedoubler.com/en/privacy-policy/
travel audience – An Amadeus Company - https://travelaudience.com/product-privacy-policy/
UDG - https://www.udg.de/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/privacy_policy_EN.pdf
usemax (Emego GmbH) - http://www.usemax.de/?l=privacy
Videology - https://videologygroup.com/en/privacy-policy/
Vimeo - https://vimeo.com/cookie_policy
Virtual Minds - https://virtualminds.de/datenschutz/
Vodafone GmbH - https://www.vodafone.de/unternehmen/datenschutz-privatsphaere.html
Waystack - https://www.wayfair.com/customerservice/general_info.php#privacy
Weborama - https://weborama.com/e-privacy/
White Ops - https://www.whiteops.com/privacy
Widespace - https://www.widespace.com/legal/privacy-policy-notice/
Yieldr - https://www.yieldr.com/privacy/
ZMS - https://zms.zalando.com/#
eBay is a registered trade mark of eBay, Inc. ezsniper.com sniper is not affiliated with eBay, Inc.
Copyright © Abercrombie Online, 2001-2020
| Privacy | Terms
